[
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "م ا ل ي و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "م ي ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "ف ي ل و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ي ن ي ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "ت ا س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "همتارو",
        "response": "ر و ت ا م ه"
    },
    {
        "question": "الويفيا",
        "response": "ي ا ي ف و ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "ي ل و ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "رايلي",
        "response": "ل ي ا ي ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "دازاي",
        "response": "ا ي ا ز د"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "و ل ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "ر ا د ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوريتشي",
        "response": "ش ي ي ت و ر ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ش ي ت ا ت ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "توبي",
        "response": "ب ي و ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "ر ا ب ا و ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ا ي ي ف ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاشيراما",
        "response": "م ا ر ا ش ي ا ه"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "ت و ر و و ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "response": "و ب س و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ي م ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "و ي س ي ش"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيد",
        "response": "ي د ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "س ا ك ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "دانزو",
        "response": "ز و ن ا د"
    },
    {
        "question": "وينغ",
        "response": "ن غ ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "تينشيهان",
        "response": "ا ن ي ه ن ش ي ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيكوهان",
        "response": "ا ن ه و ك ي ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "ج ي ا ك ي ز ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "ي ا ا ر ي ج"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوشينو",
        "response": "ه و ن و ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوكومي",
        "response": "م ي ك و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "ي و غ"
    },
    {
        "question": "تشيو",
        "response": "ي و ش ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسوري",
        "response": "ر ي و س ا س"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "و ك و ز ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "ي ا ر و د ي م"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيجي",
        "response": "ج ي ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "ت ا س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليزا",
        "response": "ز ا ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاغويا",
        "response": "ي ا غ و ا ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هينا",
        "response": "ن ا ي ه"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "ك ا و ا ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "ت ا ن ا ي ه"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينتسو",
        "response": "س و ت ن ي ز"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "ك و غ و ن ي ر"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ا ي ف ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورتا",
        "response": "ت ا ر و ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "ك ا و س ي ه"
    },
    {
        "question": "انوس",
        "response": "و ن س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "بياكوغان",
        "response": "ا ن غ و ك ي ا ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوكو",
        "response": "ك و ش و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديكو",
        "response": "ك و ي د"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "م ي ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "فانجانس",
        "response": "ن س ج ا ن ا ف"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "و س ل ي ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "تسوموغو",
        "response": "غ و م و س و ت"
    },
    {
        "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "ي م ا ن ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايزن",
        "response": "ن ز ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "زاراكي",
        "response": "ك ي ر ا ز ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوراهارا",
        "response": "ر ا ه ا ر ا و ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوي",
        "response": "و ي ي ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوهان",
        "response": "ا ن و ه غ"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيريلين",
        "response": "ي ن ل ي ر ي ك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتسورو",
        "response": "ر و س و ا ت ي ن ه"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريتشيل",
        "response": "ي ل ش ت ي ر"
    }
]
